Translated by Releska
But in the end, the dream of a man,
of course, always with you and me
That's right, that's right, that's right
If you could come with me, you'd be a great person
If you could come with me, I'd be happy
If you could come with me, you'd be happy
Your smile and your smile will all be cut off
It's you and you and you
If you can fall in love with your hands
You're way closer to the heart
I can't even remember how I feel
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
I don't know.
If we were to perform the real thing on the bus, it would be very dangerous.
We were so angry that we had to turn the world around.
I don't know where we are.
I don't know where we will be back to when we are back from.
But I didn't get bored.
My family and friends who are friends are also friends.
I was so happy to be with you.
Y-Y-Y-Y-Y!
Y-Y-Y-Y!
I'm here!
I told you to draw this magic when you don't have to go.
Gakka!
Yum-Kam-Kam!
Who is it?
Hurry!
Wow! What's going on?!
No! No!
Hey! Beard!
What's going on with that box?
Hey! This is a gift!
No! No!
Who said this is a gift?
Now...
No! No!
No!
Hey!
Hey! Beard!
What's going on with you?
I don't know who you are.
Everyone should stop.
But I don't know.
What's going on?
I don't know.
For example...
There's a stone, a stone, a stone, a stone.
There's a stone, a stone, a stone, a stone, a stone, a stone, a stone, a stone, a stone.
Hey!
What's going on with me?
I thought you were eating it.
Hey! Beard!
Hey!
The center of the city!
That's right!
Listen like this, and you'll have a hard time.
Well, I see.
So it's like a trade-off.
Come on, save him!
I'm not going to eat it!
Viva Bomi!
Wait, center!
I got it!
Ok, go ahead.
You're a little weak.
Sorry, but I'm not going to bother you.
I'm fine.
That's all you have to do.
I'm sorry.
You did a good job.
I'm still in the middle of the fire.
You have to work in the middle of the fire.
I can't become an adult!
That's right! Let's go somewhere else.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Let's go!
Where are you going?
I'm worried about my friends.
I remember them as a card.
Oh, really?
I'm looking for a big one right now.
I'll give it to you.
It might be a dangerous guy.
Yo!
Dad!
Everyone!
Zeta! Yo!
I'll give it to you right now!
It's so hot.
It's so hot!
Are you all right?
What are you doing?
That's right!
I'm the one who brought you here.
Really?
What do you want?
I want to see you.
Be careful!
Dad!
Did you believe me?
Well, I was just thinking about it.
For now, I'll take care of the shop.
Yeah!
I'll take care of you!
Hey!
Let's go!
Yeah!
I don't think I should worry about the face.
I think I should worry about the face.
I'm fine, but...
Dad!
I'm so sorry!
I was just thinking about it.
Oh!
This is a water bottle.
That means, this person has a reaction.
Really, Dad?
A reaction?
Yeah!
Even if you don't have a water bottle, can you do it?
What's wrong, Dad?
I like it.
Don't you know anything?
Huh?
I don't know anything.
Yeah.
I used to be with you when I was little.
Well, I'll be back when I'm hungry.
I'm here.
Yeah.
Okay.
I feel a bit uneasy next time.
If you were back, where did you go, quite recently?
Let me turn right away.
These days, I'm busy getting out of bed.
So, I can go home.
I'm so tired.
C'mon, C'mon, C'mon!
Baby!
Baby! C'mon!
Baby, C'mon...
Baby, C'mon!
How can I go out?
You're my wife, you know?
I have a feeling you're still not here.
I'm not here.
You should've come back here.
You're not here.
You're not there.
I mean, you could've been here
if you caught me.
Yeah, I was here.
So it's your turn!
Gengeng!
Uyum!
So cute!
Muka Muka! Muka Muka Muka wants to eat it!
There's still some food in it!
Muka Muka! Where are you going? Muka Muka!
Ah, Mr. Tosoba!
What are you doing, Tosuka?
Don't you know my Muka Muka?
It's so annoying!
Wait a minute!
Muka Muka wants to eat it!
Yes, it's so annoying!
Really?
Where are you going?
I'm sorry for yesterday!
How about this theory?
Really?
This is my father!
I can't wait to eat it!
Yesterday?
Ah! My child is going to eat it!
My child is going to eat it!
Yes, Muka Muka!
Muka Muka's child?
Yes!
Muka Muka wants to eat it!
Why do you laugh?
I'm not laughing!
Muka Muka is not laughing!
I am not laughing!
Oh, I see!
I'm not laughing!
I'M NOT LIKING!
Oh, I see!
I'm not laughing!
Muka Muka wants to eat it!
That's all!
Oh, my God!
Wait!
I'm here.
Oh, my God!
You're back?
You were really close to your hand.
Huh?
My God!
I've seen your childhood friends before.
I've been living with you for a long time.
I don't want to be in love with you.
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
I'm fine.
I'm from Bakujikara.
I've been to you for a long time.
I didn't know.
I was told to be a friend by my friends.
I'm telling you to be a friend by my side.
What's your name?
My name is Roshi Nakayoku.
Ryo-san.
Mr. Hangeo, you're back.
Yes.
I'll do my best.
Bunchi!
What?
It's so hot.
Bunchi.
Huh?
What's wrong, everyone?
I'm fine.
Mr. Hangeo,
I'm not here.
I'm here for the first time in the morning.
For the first time in the morning?
Bunchi!
Huh?
What's wrong, Mr. Hangeo?
I'm fine.
Fine?
I can't control my feelings.
I want to see your face.
Hey, Mr. Hangeo.
I can't.
I'm not a teacher at all.
I'm just a little bit uncomfortable.
It's like that.
But I can't go anywhere.
I'm here to my friend.
Yeah, I don't want you to come to Krozun.
We'll get you out of here.
Krozun!
Good morning!
Damn it!
I was so nervous that I couldn't eat at all!
Everyone's here!
Thank you!
Stop it! The rabbit is falling!
This house is also called a dive.
Look at this!
It's already a rabbit.
I'm not going to look at it either!
I'm the one who made it!
Let's see whether it's a rabbit!
Kuro!
That's a good idea.
Who cares where we go?
Kuro!
It's the rabbit!
It's getting better.
It's just that I'm going to die.
It's not like I'll always be here, right?
It's been a while.
It's been a while since I've been here.
I'm not going to sleep with that dog, but I'm going to sleep with that dog, too.
It's been a while since I've been here, right?
I don't want to go home yet, dog.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Sis, Sis, Sis, Sis, Sis.
Excuse me.
What is this?
Mr. Han Kujin.
Where are you going?
Ah, maybe,
Or maybe,
I don't want to see anyone again, so I'm going to come back soon.
I wonder if it's time to go back.
Yeah, we've got a lot of things to do with Hangeo-jin.
I thought everyone was going to kill me, so I'm going to cut it off.
I can't do anything! I don't want to see anyone again!
I'm sorry, but I don't want to do anything to Aitsan.
What the hell is going on?
I'm not the boss, but everyone is.
Yay! I'm done!
H-Hangeo-jin!
That fish...
It's full of fish and it's the best.
It's so big that you can't find it.
It's so big that you can't eat it.
But you can't eat it.
Even if it's because of this, it's amazing.
It's really hard to eat.
It's hard to eat?
It's really hard to eat?
Uru?
Yeah.
I'm here to see this world,
but I'm not sure if it's going to be a big deal or not.
I see.
I think it'd be nice to have more people like you
to have more fun in the future.
I see.
Alright, I'll take you to my place.
Oh, my God. I'm so hungry.
I'm so hungry.
Now, let's get to the party!
Yay!
It's time for the party!
Everyone, come here, baby!
Eh!?
欸!?
Ugh!!
Oiii!
Oh, really?
What are you saying?
What?
Well, so...
I almost killed you...
I'll kill my boss...
What?
You don't have to worry about me, do you?
Don't worry then, you shouldn't be that simple!
Huh?
What are you talking about?
A gentle,инny,anny,anny...
It's a seal. What do you think?
It's a seal.
Can you do that, Mitsukura-sai?
I don't know.
This is Mitsuda's daughter.
That's great.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
That's great, Oji.
The first guest is Mr. Hangyoji.
Right?
Oh, look!
I'll do it!
I'm so sorry, Oji.
The island is totally ruined.
Mr. Hangyoji, you might not be able to come back to Japan.
No, it's not.
I didn't think I'd let you come home.
But you can't go back any more.
Oji from Miyagi-san,
Mr. Hangyoji!
It's so hard, so're you!
I'll give you back my love.
I'll let you pass my love.
Thank you so much for doing this.
Bi-ya-no it's a fun walk.
I'll go to a new place.
No, no!
Never dangerous!
Translated by Releska
I feel so bad all day.
We didn't meet you before.
I'm with you, she's with me.
I'm having a difficult time.
I can't stop myself.
I'll feel her sleep all day.
I feel so much better.
I could never relax.
I feel so sorry.
I feel sorry.
in the heart
Bam, ba, ba, bam, noise
Bam, b I at you
Bam, ba, bam, wave
This is the party
Let's play
Nice, wish, wish, wish, wish, wish
Be quiet
Everybody
It's done
It has all been
ax up
장
One, let's take a break
Let's sing
Let's go
The next episode
Huh? A reaction letter?
A reaction letter is a story that has a secret story
So, if you have a map in this world, it's a joke!
It's not a map, it's a map!
Huh? What's that?
It's a little bit of a mystery!
Next, a secret paradise
Set up a good fight
Let's go!